{
    "subject": "Blair_Cramer",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Todd_Manning",
    "human_readable": "Blair Cramer is married to Todd Manning.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9882194995880127,
            "question": "Is Todd Manning married to Blair Cramer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8606513142585754,
            "question": "Who is Blair Cramer married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7962113618850708,
            "question": "What type of relationship exists between Blair Cramer and Todd Manning?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7912596464157104,
            "question": "Who are Blair Cramer and Todd Manning connected by?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7274841070175171,
            "question": "Name the husband of Blair Cramer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6764781475067139,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Todd Manning?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.607897162437439,
            "question": "What is the name of Blair Cramer's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12273336946964264,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in a marriage relationship according to the provided information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10125400125980377,
            "question": "According to the statement, who is in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08854427188634872,
            "question": "Does the given information describe a marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Blair Cramer is married to Todd Manning.",
            "html": "yago_30347_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=According to the statement, who is in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_30347_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the individuals involved in a marriage relationship according to the provided information?",
            "html": "yago_30347_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Blair Cramer's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30347_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30347_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30347_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30347_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30347_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30347_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30347_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30347_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30347_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30347_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30347_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that the statement \"Blair Cramer is married to Todd Manning\" is supported by the documents.\n\nHere is the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Blair Cramer is married to Todd Manning.\" Multiple references in the documents indicate their multiple marriages, such as this excerpt from `52.txt`: \"and her ex-hubby \u2014 Todd Manning (Roger Howarth)\", and also mentions of their daughter Starr, which is a clear indication of their marital status."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}